gingersoftware.com 2011-01-31

# Privacy Policy | Ginger Software

Thank you for visiting www.gingersoftware.com, Ginger Software, Inc.’s website (hereafter referred to as the “Site”). Your privacy is important to us, and we have implemented policies designed to protect your privacy (hereafter referred to as the “Privacy Policy”).  Please review the Privacy Policy carefully, which will explain our online information gathering practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at the Site. The Company may amend the Privacy Policy, from time to time, by updating this posting, so you should visit this page periodically to review the Privacy Policy as then in effect.  If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Software or the services available at the Site.  USE OF THE SOFTWARE AND/OR THE SERVICES CONSTITUTES YOUR ACCEPTANCE AND AGREEMENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

Capitalized terms used and not otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meanings set forth in the Ginger Software End-User License Agreement (the “EULA”), which you can find at the Site.

**Information collection and use**

When you visit the Site, we collect your IP address and standard web log information, such as your browser type and the pages you accessed on our website.

If you wish to download our Software and use our on-line services, we will collect the following types of information from you:

1         Technical information – the browser type and operation system on your computer.

We do not ask that you furnish your name, age, address or other “Personal Information”, which is information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that specific person. 

When you use our Software, your computer communicates with our server on the internet.  Any information that you furnish to our server on the internet will be treated by the Company in accordance with the terms of the EULA, which provides among other things that, with the exception of Personal Information, any communication or material that you transmit to the Company through the Site by electronic e-mail or otherwise, including any data, questions, comments, suggestions and the like, is and will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary information, which the Company may use for any purpose whatsoever without compensation to you, including disclosure, reproduction or publication.    

We will also collect a username and password used to ensure that only you have access to any of the Personal Information you have provided and to your user account. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any password you use to register, and you should always be careful whenever disclosing information on line, particularly information or material that contains any Personal Information.

Finally, we may also collect additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, we may collect information related to your contact with our customer support team when you respond to a survey.

Information collected through the Site and the Service may be stored and processed in any countries in which the Company or its service providers host their server farms. You therefore understand and consent that your information may be transferred outside of the country in which you reside.

**Information collection by means of technology **

The Company uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences and to record session information to customize Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. The Company does not link the information stored in cookies to any Personal Information you submit while on the Site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set, in accordance with each browser’s preferences (check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences). However, we recommend that you enable cookies from the Company in order to use all functions on the Site.

**Protection of Personal Information **

We take appropriate precautions to protect any Personal Information that you submit to us.   **__**

The Company's user accounts are secured by user-created passwords. Since a user account may contain Personal Information (e.g., an e-mail address that contains a person’s real name), the Company takes precautions to insure that user account information is kept private. The Company uses reasonable measures to protect user information that is stored within our database, and restricts access to user information to those who are responsible to operate and maintain the Site, including employees and service providers of the Company, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that the Company cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time. Please do not transmit any private or confidential information to the Company by email or through the Site. The Company cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted over the internet. Regardless of the precautions taken by you or by the Company, “perfect security” does not exist on the internet. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk. 

For any additional information about the security measures we use on the Site, please contact us at [Support@gingersoftware.com](mailto:Support@gingersoftware.com).

**Use of Personal Information** **and disclosure**

We may from time to time disclose Personal Information to third parties without your prior consent in the following circumstances:  (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by the Company, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; or (2) to enforce the terms of the EULA or otherwise to protect the Company’s rights in the Software and Services or the rights of the Company’s customers to enjoy the benefits of the Software and Services.  We do not furnish any Personal Information to any third parties for marketing purposes.  We do reserve the right to transfer Personal Information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of the Company or any of its assets.

**  Links to other sites**

The Site contains links to other sites. The Company is not responsible and has no liability for privacy policies and/or practices used by other sites. We strongly advise you to read the privacy policy stated on other sites you link to through the Site. Our Privacy Policy only governs information that we collect on the Site. ****

**Notifications and updates**

The Site may also send you notifications regarding updates to the Site and the Service. We may also communicate with you to provide requested services and with respect to issues relating to your account via email or phone. You will not be able to opt out of service announcements that contain important information about the Service. ****

**How you can contact us about privacy questions**

The Company cares deeply about online privacy. For any questions, comments and remarks concerning this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at [Support@Gingersoftware.com](mailto:Support@Gingersoftware.com).
